Finding aid for the Getty Education Institute for the Arts, Grant Files, 1984-2001 IA10021
Institutional Records and Archives
- Regional Institute grants, 1986-2001; II.; 61 Linear Feet (64 boxes)
  - Regional Grant Recipients
    - Prairie Visions: The Nebraska Consortium (Nebraska Department of Education):
      - Implementation:
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1995 (Year 6):
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Progress Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Institute Materials, Summer 1995 (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Loose Papers and Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-32)
          - Loose Papers and Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - National Specialty, Fiscal Year 1995:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Grant Offer Letter, October 12, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Progress Report September, November, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Progress Report December 1994 to March 1995 (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - National Specialty, Fiscal Year 1996: (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - October Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - December Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - April Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - Core Program, Fiscal Year 1996 (Year 7):
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - October Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - December Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - April Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - [Loose 1996 Summer Institute Materials (assorted manuals and reports)] (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
        - National Specialty, Fiscal Year 1997:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Progress Report, October 1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - January 1998 Report (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
          - Collateral Material (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - Core Program, Fiscal Year 1997:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Summer Institute Schedule/Program Guide, June 14-19, 1998 (loose) (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - January 1998 Report (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Prairie Visions, Fiscal Year 1997, Core Program: (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Correspondence [2 files] (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - June 24, 1997 Leadership Dinner (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Original and Revised Fiscal Year 1997 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-34)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - June 1997, Leadership Academy Notebook (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - [Loose Nebraska Department of Education, Prairie Visions Summer Institute 1997, Core Program (Year 10)] (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Fiscal Year 1998:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - January 1998 report (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Fiscal Year 1999:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Core Program, FY 2000:
          - Budget, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
          - Correspondence, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
          - Grant offer letter, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
          - Collateral materials, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
          - Internal memos, FY 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
          - Summer Institute materials, FY 2000; (2 folders and 1 VHS videocassette) (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Core, FY 2001:
          - Budget, FY 2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-04)
          - Correspondence, FY 2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-04)
          - Grant offer letters, FY 2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-04)
          - Internal memos, FY 2001 (Box 2010.IA.21-04)
      - Strategic Planning Grant:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - SPG Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - Implementation Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - Vision Statement (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
        - Technical Assistance Visit (Box 2007.IA.16-33)
      - Student Assessment:
        - Year One, Fiscal Year 1990, Student Assessment Proposal & Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Year Two, Fiscal Year 1991, Student Assessment Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Year Two, Fiscal Year 1991, Student Assessment Grant, Contract (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Year Three, Fiscal Year 1992, Student Assessment Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Year Four, Fiscal Year 1993, Student Assessment Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Year Five, Fiscal Year 1994, Student Assessment Project, Grant Letter, Ap. (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Prairie Visions, Fiscal Year 1995 (year 6), Student Assessment Project (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Prairie Visions, Fiscal Year 1996 (year 7), Student Assessment Project (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
        - Prairie Visions, Fiscal Year 1997 (year 8), Student Assessment Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-35)
      - Nebraska Arts Council [original grant award letters], 1998 (Box 2009.IA.38-02)
      - Nebraska Department of Education [original grant award letters], 1987-1999 (Box 2009.IA.38-02)
    - Rhode Island School of Design:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
      - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
      - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
      - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
      - Grant Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
      - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
      - Planning Grant Report (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
      - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-56)
    - Southeast Institute for Education in the Visual Arts (University of Tennessee at Chattanooga):
      - Planning:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Grant Offer Letter, May 22, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Planning Grant Report (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Grant Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - [Loose Proposal Report] (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
      - Implementation:
        - Year One:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Site Visit – Summer,1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Grant Offer Letter, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Grant Proposal, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Summer Institute Notebook, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Fiscal Agent (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
        - Year Two:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-46)
          - Grant Proposal, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Grant Offer Letter, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Fiscal Agent (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Student Assessment Proposal and Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - The Southeast Institute for Education in the Visual Arts: Bi-Annual Report, January 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - The Southeast Institute for Education in the Visual Arts: Bi-Annual Report, May 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
        - Year Three:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Grant Offer Letter, May 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Interim Report – Memos 1 & 2 (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Annual Report for 1991 and Proposal for 1992, March 1, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Student Assessment Grant, Contract (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Student Assessment Proposal and Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
        - Year Four:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Grant Offer Letter, June 13, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - Internal Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-47)
          - [Loose papers and reports] (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
        - Year Five:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
          - [Loose Papers and Reports] (Box 2007.IA.16-48)
          - [Loose Papers and Reports] (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - [Loose papers and reports] (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - Student Assessment Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
        - Year Six:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - For Year 1993 Project Report/For Year 1994 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-49)
          - Collateral Materials (Summ. Institute) (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
        - National Specialty, Fiscal Year 1995:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Grant Offer Letter 10/13/94 (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Loose Papers (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Progress Report, September to November 1994 (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Progress Report, 12/94 to 3/95 (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Progress Report, 4/95 to 8/95 (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1995:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Progress Report, June to August 1994, Summer Institute Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
        - National Specialty, Fiscal Year 1996:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - October Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - April Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1996:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - RIG Travel Fund Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-51)
          - December Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-52)
          - [Loose: Southeast Institute for Education in the Visual Arts: October 1 Report Attachments] (Box 2007.IA.16-52)
          - Loose: Satellite Institute Notebook (Box 2007.IA.16-52)
          - Loose: Satellite Institute Program Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-52)
          - October Progress Reports and 1995 Summer Institute Materials and Attachments (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
          - Summer 1996 Renewal (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
        - Core Progress Report for 4/1/96 through 8/30/96 (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
          - Attachments: (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - Advisory Board Meetings Minutes and Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - Renewal Institute Notebook and Evaluations (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - SIEVA Two-Week Institute Planning (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - SIEVA/SCEA Two-Week Institute Notebook and Evaluations (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - Participant Acceptance Notification (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - SIEVA Intern List and Notebook (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - Administrator's Leadership Institute Participant List and Notebook (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - Mississippi Leadership Institute Participant List and Notebook (Box 2007.IA.16-53)
            - North Georgia Institute Notebook and Evaluations (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
            - Alabama Institute Notebook and Evaluations (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
            - Savannah Institute Notebook and Evaluations (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
            - Director's Meetings Minutes (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
            - District Contact Year-End Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
            - SIEVA Assistant Director Resignation Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
            - Georgia Challenge Grant Guidelines (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
            - FY1996 SIEVA Final Budget Report (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
            - Annenberg Applications and Information (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1997:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Original and Revised for 1997 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Database Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1998:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - TETAC Administrator's Meeting (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-54)
          - [Loose Report: Southeast Center for Education in the Visual Arts: Summer Multi-Arts Institute June 22-26, 1998] (Box 2007.IA.16-55)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1999:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-55)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-55)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-55)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-55)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 2000:
          - Budget (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Correspondence (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Internal Memos (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Collateral Material (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 2001:
          - Correspondence (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Internal Memos (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Budget (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Collateral (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Grant Offer (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
        - Browns Mill Elementary School information packet, 2000-2001; undated (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
        - Southeast Center for Education in the Arts, December 2000 (Box 2010.IA.21-03)
      - Strategic Planning Grant, June 15, 1993 to April 1, 1994
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
        - SPG Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
        - Implementation Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-50)
      - University of Tennessee at Chattanooga [original grant award letters], 1988-1998; (2 folders) (Box 2009.IA.38-01)
  - Regional Grant Reviews and Evaluations
    - Planning Grant Program Review:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Guidelines for Review (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Reviewers' Comments (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - 1987 LA Institute Observation (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - List of Applicants and Rejectees (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
    - Implementation Grant Review, Fall 1987:
      - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Correspondence with Reviewers (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Guidelines for Review (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Meeting Notes and Agenda, 12/14/87 (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Site Visits (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Meeting Notes and Agenda, 10/26/87 (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
    - Implementation Grant Review, Spring 1988:
      - Correspondence with Reviewers (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Meeting Notes and Agenda, 5/9/88 (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Site Visits (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Meeting Notes and Agenda, 6/17/88 (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
    - Evaluation Project:
      - Year 1, 1988-1989:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Correspondence with Brent Wilson (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - November 1988 Cross-Site Evaluation Report (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Contract/Proposal, Wilson, for year 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Loose Papers (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Summer 1989 Institutional Reports & Cross-Site (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Winter 1989 Institutional Reports & Cross-Site (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Year 2, 1989-1990:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Correspondence with Brent Wilson (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Contract/Proposal, Wilson, for year 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - 1990 Cross-Site/Evaluation Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
      - Year 3, 1990-1991:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Correspondence with Brent Wilson (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-61)
        - Contract/Proposal, Wilson, for year 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Fall 1990 Report (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
      - Year 4, 1991-1992:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - "Interim Report" Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Contracts with Wilson and Penn State (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Confidential Memos, 9/1/91 (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Memos to Project Directors, 9/1/91 (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Evaluation Instruments/Questionnaires (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Spring and Summer 1991 Evaluations (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Report (Cross-Site Evaluation) (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - "Interim Report" (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Recommendation Summaries (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
      - Year 5, 1992-1993:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Contract (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Site and Cross-Site Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Cross-Site Evaluation, Summer 1992 (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
        - Evaluation Instruments/Questionnaires (Box 2007.IA.16-62)
      - National Evaluation Project for Year 1995:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Correspondence with Team Members (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Proposals (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Contracts, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Elementary Implementation Survey, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
      - National Evaluation Project for Year 1996:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Computers (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Summer 1995 Site Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Contracts, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.16-63)
        - Summer 1995 Cross-Site Report (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
      - Evaluation, Summer 1996:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Contracts (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Summer 1996 Institute Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Visual Arts Research Article (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Report on Pilot Study of Teacher Bfs (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
      - Evaluation, Summer 1997 (Rubin):
        - Pilot Study of Student Outcomes (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Summer 1997 RIG Program Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Evaluation Plan for 1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - NAEC Steering Committee Report (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Contracts (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Cross-Site Report (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
  - Regional Grants Administration
    - Regional Institute Meetings:
      - Team Meeting, April 1988: (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - List of Attendees (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Meeting Notes and Agenda (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
      - Team Meeting, December 1988: (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Correspondence/Memos to Directors (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Notes, Agenda (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Radisson Hotel (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - List of Attendees (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Fact Sheets (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Sacramento & Fresno (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
      - Directors' Meeting, April 1989: (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - List of Attendees (Box 2007.IA.16-64)
        - Meeting Notes (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Vitas and Speaker Profiles (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
      - Team Meeting, Spring 1990: (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Correspondence with Directors and Speakers (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Correspondence with Vendors/Hotel (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Meeting Notes/Agenda (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Participant List (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Participant Packets (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
      - Directors' Meeting, Fall 1990: (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Budget/Contracts (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Correspondence with Participants and Speaker (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Correspondence with Vendors Including Hotel (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Participant List (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Meeting Notes/Agenda (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Photographs (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
      - Directors' Meeting, January 1991: (Box 2007.IA.16-65)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-65)